lafeber.com 2019-04-09

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Rights - Lafeber Company

Last Updated: May 22, 2018

This website (“Site”) is owned and operated by Lafeber Company (“Lafeber”, “we”, “our”, or “us”). Lafeber takes your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy describes what information this Site gathers about you, how we use that information, and what steps we take to protect that information.  
By using this Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as the Site’s Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason and without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy on this site. Please check back periodically for up-to-date information about our privacy practices.

###  **1\. What information does Lafeber Company collect about me?**

This Site collects information about you to provide and improve our services, communicate offers that we believe will interest you, and to administer our business. We collect personal information from you when you submit that information to us voluntarily. For example, we collect information from you when you create an account on the Site, communicate with our customer service team, or make a purchase through the Site. We also record information when you contact us, including customer service requests and notes or details explaining what you asked and how we responded.

The personal information we collect may include the following: name, user ID, password, e-mail address, shipping address, phone number, demographic information (gender, age), financial information (such as credit card or bank account numbers), buying or selling information regarding the products you purchase, information about your purchasing preferences and interests, technical information like your internet protocol (IP) address, your device operating system and browser type, your referring website’s address, and your clickstream through our Site, or web beacons that allow us to know what pages on our Site have been visited, what e-mails have been opened, and if our banner ads have been effective.

If you register at this Site or opt-in to receive e-mails, newsletters, or other offers or communications, we collect and store the information provided. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features including customization and communications.

Our Site may also collect information about the location of your device. Your device should require you to provide permission before our Site obtains location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, and/or cell towers. We and our service providers may use this information, along with other information submitted by you, to provide you with personalized content from location-based services.

We may automatically receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our Site, our e-mails, and/or our online advertisements. This information helps us to make our Site work more efficiently, evaluate use of our Site, and support our website analytics and marketing campaigns.

###  **2\. How does Lafeber Company use information about me?**

We use information about you to deliver, improve, update and enhance the services we provide to you. We collect personal information from you when you submit that information to us voluntarily. For example, we collect information from you when you create an account on the Site, communicate with our customer service team, or make a purchase through the Site.

The personal information we collect may include the following: name, user ID, password, e-mail address, shipping address, phone number, demographic information (gender, age), financial information (such as credit card or bank account numbers), buying or selling information regarding the products you purchase, information about your purchasing preferences and interests, technical information like your internet protocol (IP) address, your device operating system and browser type, your referring website’s address, and your clickstream through our Site, or web beacons that allow us to know what pages on our Site have been visited, what e-mails have been opened, and if our banner ads have been effective.

If you register at this Site or opt-in to receive e-mails, newsletters, or other offers or communications, we collect and store the information provided. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features including customization and communications.

Our Site may also collect information about the location of your device. Your device should require you to provide permission before our Site obtains location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, and/or cell towers. We and our service providers may use this information, along with other information submitted by you, to provide you with personalized content from location-based services.

 **Cookies**  
Like most other websites, our Site uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that identify the web browser on a particular computer. When you visit lafeber.com, cookies will be sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us recognize your device and provide more customized services. For instance, we use cookies to analyze the frequency and duration of visits, traffic statistics from members and non-members, preferences, interests, review of products, etc. We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. The information we gather using cookies enables us to improve your experience with Lafeber through targeted marketing and customization features. You can choose to reject our cookies by changing your browser preferences. If you choose to block our cookies, however, you will not be able to benefit from some of our services including personalization. If you disable, block, or delete cookies, not all of the tracking described in this Privacy Policy will stop.

 **Children Under 13 Years of Age**  
This Site is directed to adults, and does not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13, and you believe your child has provided personal information to our Site that you would like us to delete, please contact us at privacy@lafeber.com.

###  **3\. Does Lafeber Company share my data with third parties?**

We may share your personal data with affiliated Emeraid LLC sister company. Examples of when we share data include processing payments, communicating with you through surveys or email. We only share the minimum information necessary, and third parties are prohibited from using your information for any other purpose as indicated in our privacy policy.

The information we collect on this Site may be used to: support our core business functions; facilitate the processing of payment transactions; keep track of your previous service purchases or offerings; respond to requests and inquiries; provide support services; communicate with you; send administrative information, such as changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; administer promotions or contests; facilitate social sharing functionality; analyze and monitor usage of our services to make improvements; help secure our services, prevent fraud, and enforce our policies; help personalize our services; to make contact, directly or through a third-party vendor, to complete a survey or questionnaire; conduct data analysis and research, audits, develop new products, identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and to operate and expand our business activities; and perform other activities with your consent. You can sign up for our e-mail list by providing your e-mail address through our Site services.

To accomplish these purposes, we may combine information about you that we collect online and from third party sources. Please note that laws vary from jurisdiction to jurisdiction, and so laws and regulations relating to privacy and data disclosure, applicable to the places where your information is transferred to or stored, used, or processed in, may be different from the laws and regulations applicable to the place where you are a resident.

We may make third party services, including third party applications, available to you on this Site.

We may share the information we collect about you (including personally identifiable information) only as follows: as necessary to perform our services and to complete payment transactions; with companies and vendors that help us to operate our business by providing services such as payment processing, website hosting, fraud screening, data analysis, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, e-mail delivery, auditing and other similar services; with third parties that have contracted with us to perform certain functions on our behalf; with third parties sponsors of promotions or contests where consent has been given; to comply with law or other legal obligations such as responding to subpoenas, or other requests from public and government agencies, including laws and other legal obligations outside a party’s country of residence; to protect our rights, operations or property, or that of our users; to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential or suspected illegal activities, fraud, threats to the personal safety of any person, or violations of our terms of use; with other companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Lafeber that support the provision of transaction services or relationship with a party, including subsidiaries and parent companies both present and future; with a purchaser of all or a unit of Lafeber (or the majority of Lafeber’s or its unit’s assets), a merger, acquisition, or internal reorganization of Lafeber or a unit of Lafeber; with your consent.

 **Third Party Websites**  
The Site may include links to third-party websites, including social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest. Third-party websites are not bound by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the content on or policies governing any third-party website. We encourage you to review the privacy policy and terms of use for any third-party website you visit. Please note that any information posted to public areas such as on our social media pages may be seen by other visitors or the general public.

 **4\. Does Lafeber Company keep your information secure?**

Lafeber works to protect your personal information. Lafeber Company uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alternation or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. Lafeber Company uses security measures including and not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. All sensitive information is collected on a dedicated secure server provided and managed by World known hosting Company. It protects from DDoS attack (UDP flood).The Hosting Company has an extensive custom firewall rule and large mod security rule sets protecting servers from a variety of forms of attack. If the servers experience heavy flooding, datacenters enable network level flood protection. The datacenters are all highly secure facilities with restricted access. Also the hosting Company employs additional server security methods and precautions that are confidential. While our Site strives to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, Lafeber cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party hackers from illegally obtaining this information. When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology.

We also urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your Site password(s) with anyone and follow Password security rules, such as lengthy passwords including uppercase letters, numbers and special characters.

In case of Data Breach the Lafeber Company will inform all their Customers about it within 72 hours using e-mail.

###  **5\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a California resident and a Lafeber customer, you have the right to request information from us once per calendar year regarding the customer information we share with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an e-mail to privacy@lafeber.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you via an e-mail response.

###  **6\. EU GDPR UPDATES**

  *  **Request a copy of your personal data.**

You may request a copy of your personal data in an electronic format that you can take to other service providers. We will respond to your request within 30 days by providing a link to a location where the data can be downloaded.

  *  **Request account closure and deletion of your personal data.**

You may request to close your account. You will no longer be able to log in to your account after it is closed. Upon closing your account, you may request that your personal data be deleted. It may take up to 30 days for account data to be deleted.

###  **7\. How can I update my personal information?**

You are in control of your personal information. [See Your choices about data we collect to learn more.](https://lafeber.com/main/your-choices-about-data-we-collect/ "See Your Choices")

© 2018 Lafeber Company. All Rights Reserved.
